{
    "subject": "resource/Bat_Boy:_The_Musical",
    "predicate": "ontology/basedOn",
    "object": "resource/Weekly_World_News",
    "human_readable": "Bat Boy: The Musical is based on Weekly World News.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.898678719997406,
            "question": "What is Bat Boy: The Musical based on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6926262974739075,
            "question": "Why do you think Weekly World News was chosen as the basis for a musical?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6287705898284912,
            "question": "How might the tone of Weekly World News influence the musical?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6259965300559998,
            "question": "Name the publication that inspired Bat Boy: The Musical."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5488206148147583,
            "question": "What genre is Bat Boy: The Musical likely to be classified as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5204347372055054,
            "question": "What themes might Bat Boy: The Musical explore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4840181767940521,
            "question": "What kind of audience might Bat Boy: The Musical appeal to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4781337380409241,
            "question": "Is Bat Boy: The Musical a real story or a fictional work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.475094735622406,
            "question": "Could Bat Boy: The Musical be considered a satire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40833717584609985,
            "question": "What kind of publication is Weekly World News?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bat Boy: The Musical is based on Weekly World News.",
            "html": "dbpedia_332_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could Bat Boy: The Musical be considered a satire?",
            "html": "dbpedia_332_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Bat Boy: The Musical a real story or a fictional work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_332_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of audience might Bat Boy: The Musical appeal to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_332_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_332_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_332_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_332_155.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_332_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_332_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_332_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_332_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_332_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_332_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_332_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information, I can evaluate the query \"Bat Boy: The Musical is based on Weekly World News\".\n\nThe output of this evaluation is:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents mention that \"Based on a story in The Weekly World News\" followed by a description of Bat Boy: The Musical. Therefore, there is strong evidence to support the triple that Bat Boy: The Musical is based on Weekly World News."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that \"BAT BOY: THE MUSICAL\" is based on a story from The Weekly World News, supporting the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}